Marco Predari

Fullstack Architect focused on ship robust and good quality software.

⊕ Milano, Italy, CET

predorock@gmail.com
+393336823157



About

Hello there, here's Marco, 10 years of experience as **Software Engineer** in the software industry. I headed my career path to **Software Architect** roles in start-ups and in consultancy. I think to be the missing piece for companies aiming to create great quality products without sacrificing productivity and delivery.

Based in Milan, but frequently around the Globe, I've great experience in Remote working even before pandemic.

Last, but not least, I'm an incredible bartender. Why is that relevant? Company events can be funnier than ever expected, isn't it?

Work Experience

Greenovation Remote 2024 - Present

Tech Lead

Developed a new set of web simulators to help customer to improve houses energy efficiency and increase money saving.

Spindox Labs - Ublique Remote

2023 - Present

Cloud & Integration Architect

Designed the new infrastructure based on microservices, terraform and k8s on AWS. Worked alongside pre-sale and solution managers to support the customer acquisition. Created data integration patterns to bring the customer data quickly.

Spindox Labs - Ublique Remote

2023 - 2022

Tech Team Lead

Leading a group of four devs responsible to develop and maintain the core of ublique platform (Java microservices).

Design a new pipeline and versioning system for software CI/CD.

Spindox Hybrid 2020 - 2022

Fullstack Developer

Led the team to the adoption of the Monorepo Pattern for Angular2 projects. Developed Cordova apps to manage Microsoft Dynamics CRM data.

IOOOTA / Jarvis 2018 - 2020

Cordova Developer

Smart home mobile app to perform energy analisys on business buildings.

Horsa Remote 2016 - 2020

Cordova Developer → Fullstack Developer

Developed Mobile applications based on cordova and Ionic.

Early adopter of the Google Firebase Platform and Cloud Run.

Design a custom role engine (Java Drools) for employees satisfaction analisys.

Digitag 2015 - 2016

Fullstack Developer

 $\hbox{E-Commerce Software Developer with wordpress and prestashop. Developed taylor made software solutions for the art auction market.}$

Foowd freelance 2013 - 2014

Fullstack Developer

Created a E-Commerce based on Elgg framework for gorceries social buying.

BigThink intern 2013 - 2014

Angular Developer

Developed AngularJS applications for the Facebook app market.

Design and conribute to the company framework to fast devliver fullstack applications (Laravel, AngularJS).

Education

Università degli studi di Milano

2007 - 2010

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Music Science

Skills

JavaScript TypeScript React/Next.js Node.js Java Gradle Kubernetes Terraform AWS

Projects

Ublique

Ublique is a decision support system composed of a suite of vertical solutions created to help managers in the design and management of complex systems and processes.

Tech Lead Architect React Java Micronaut AWS
Terraform Docker K8S